Guide to the Carl Woodring collection on Charles Ricketts and Charles Shannon,1846-2001, bulk 1898-1986 MS 513
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Exhibition and Auction Catalogs, 1895-1997, undated, 238619; A collection of printed and bound exhibition and auction catalogs. Includes The Society of Twelve, First Exhibition (1904) with a preface by Laurence Binyon and Charles H. Shannon. Seven Reproductions of Fifteen Pictures Shown at the Leicester Galleries in January, 1907 with a preface by Laurence Binyon.
  - Exhibition and auction catalogs, Ricketts and Shannon, 1904-1997, undated, 238621 (Box 6)
  - Exhibition and auction catalog, Ricketts, Shannon and others, 1895-1970, undated, 238620 (Box 7)
- Series VIII: Card Files, circa 1965 - 2002, 238617
  - Card files kept by Dr. Carl Woodring on works, catalogs, books, and other material related to Ricketts and Shannon., 238618 (Box 8)
- Series IX: Addendum, 238593
  - Works, 238607
    - Biographical, 238616 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Paintings, drawings, illustrations (slides), 238615 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Paintings, drawings, illustrations (photos), 238614 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Paintings, drawings, illustrations (photocopies), 238613 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Book covers & bindings, 238612 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Set & costume designs, 238611 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Sculpture, 238610 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Description of works, 238609 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Works by others, 238608 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 238594
    - Ricketts, 238606 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Shannon, 238605 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence Binyon, 238604 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Gordon Bottomley, 238603 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Sturge Moore, 238602 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Carl Woodring, 238601 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Others, 238600 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence & invoices-works by Ricketts, 238599 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence & invoices-works by Shannon, 238598 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence & invoices-works by others, 238597 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Invoices-books re: R&S, 238596 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Vale Press ephemera & other books-listings & appraisals, 238595 (Box 10, Folder 5)